[
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 [] b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a ! b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-5 ; -7) + (2 @ -4)) [] ((-9 [] -2) ! (6 * 1))) [] (((7 - 6) [] (6 + -6)) * ((-2 [] 9) ; (-1 - 5))))\nLet B = ((((9 ; 7) [] (6 * 7)) [] ((2 ! -2) + (3 [] -6))) ; (((1 - 8) + (-5 @ -5)) ; ((-4 - 10) ; (-3 @ 6))))\nLet C = ((((-10 ! -1) ! (-5 + -6)) @ ((-8 + 5) * (-10 + 10))) ; (((-3 - 3) ; (2 [] -5)) - ((2 * 9) - (-8 [] 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-10038"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(2 - b) ~ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a * a) : b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(b ][ a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a ][ b) - a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((8 * -10) ; 7) ][ -6) ; -6) ; 1) ~ -8) ~ -8) ; -2) ~ -6) ; 1) + 5) ; 7) ][ -3) - -7) + -1)\nLet B = ((((-4 : 4) - (-6 + -8)) : ((6 ~ 1) - (8 : 6))) * (((-2 ~ -10) * (-2 : 4)) : ((8 ; 8) : (-10 - -7))))\nLet C = ((((-8 * -3) ; (5 ; -3)) : ((10 * -7) + (7 ~ -7))) * (((10 * 9) : (5 ; -8)) + ((-5 : -3) * (1 ~ 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "16624"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(b - a) ][ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) ][ a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a >< a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b >< b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a >< b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-4 ! -1) @ (-9 ][ 8)) @ ((1 - -9) >< (9 * 6))) + (((8 + 1) + (6 + 2)) ][ ((1 ][ -5) + (3 ! -8))))\nLet B = ((((-3 + -10) * (6 >< 4)) >< ((-1 ][ -4) ][ (5 ][ -5))) * (((10 @ 8) * (3 + -2)) * ((8 @ 8) * (-6 >< 5))))\nLet C = ((((1 ! -10) + (-1 - -4)) ! ((7 @ 5) * (9 @ 4))) - (((-9 * -1) * (9 >< 1)) >< ((5 >< -7) + (7 ][ 10)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-18836"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a >< b$.\n$a # b$ equals $(a >< b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a >< -b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((1 >< 1) + 5) + -10) >< 8) # 10) ; 6) - 8) # -10) # 3) * 3) - -10)\nLet B = ((((-6 - 2) >< (7 # -7)) - ((-2 * 3) ; (-9 ; 10))) + (((3 >< -10) : (-5 - 9)) >< ((-6 ; -2) # (4 ; 1))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((-1 - -10) >< 6) * -10) + -9) - -6) ; -7) ; -3) # -2) # -6) # 2) # 10) + 10).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-44"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 - b) ; a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((9 ! 5) ~ (5 & 3)) ! ((-9 - -8) * (-8 * -2))) ; (((-9 ; 10) + (-1 ~ 3)) ! ((9 + 5) ~ (4 + 3))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((10 ! 5) - -6) & -10) ; 7) ; 2) * 9) ! 6) ~ 6) * -10) ! 5) ~ -4) * 5) + -2) ; 9) * -9) * 4) ; 9)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((-9 ; -2) - -10) - -1) ! -2) & -3) + 4) ! 5) ~ 9) ~ -7) ~ 3) ~ -10) ; 7) + 10) ; -5) ~ 8).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-226"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a + a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a ~ b)$ if $a ][ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((2 + -4) ][ 7) + -2) * 2) ; 4) * -6) ; 7) & 7) + 6) + 9) ; -6) ~ -1) & 5) ; 1)\nLet B = ((((1 - -4) - (2 & 4)) ][ ((-3 - -5) ~ (4 + -7))) & (((5 & -4) + (-5 * -8)) + ((7 ; -5) ~ (-7 ~ 5))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((-9 + 4) - -1) + 5) ; 7) & -2) * -1) ~ 1) - -2) - -1) + 2) ][ 6) ; -9) ; 3) ; -6) * -3) ][ 5) ~ 2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "75805"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a & b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a >< b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((-9 + -8) + 2) + -7) & -6) ! 5) ; -6) - -7) * -8) & -1) + 2) * -9)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((-1 * 2) & 5) ! 7) & -2) + -1) >< -5) - -2) * -5) ; 7) ; 9) & -9) + -1) ! 5) + 6) ; 8) ! 1)\nLet C = ((((-4 + 7) * (8 * -8)) ! ((10 & 10) >< (8 ! 8))) - (((1 & -1) ! (6 ! 7)) ! ((8 ; -7) & (-9 + 6)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "1798"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a * a) [] b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) [] a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ][ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a [] b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((-7 <> 7) ][ -1) - 3) ][ 6) ][ 7) [] 9) <> -5) ; -8) ][ -8) * -5) ; -6) - 8) * -2) ; -5) + 1)\nLet B = ((((4 + 3) ][ (2 <> 8)) + ((-1 + 7) ][ (9 * 6))) * (((6 ; -3) [] (7 <> 2)) ][ ((-3 - 1) * (3 ; -3))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((-8 * -1) <> 10) [] 8) + -5) - 9) [] 8) <> 1) ; 4) <> -7) ; 6) [] 5) * -1) ][ 8) ][ -7) * 3) + -9) * 2) * 6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-50560"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a [] a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b [] b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 + b) ; a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((-7 ; -1) : (-6 * 2)) * ((7 [] -2) ; (8 * -9))) - (((-3 - 5) & (-9 * 6)) + ((-8 * 2) ; (9 * 6))))\nLet B = ((((5 [] -7) & (7 - 8)) * ((-6 * -10) + (-8 & 4))) [] (((-7 ; -4) & (3 & -5)) * ((-8 [] -2) [] (-10 ; 5))))\nLet C = ((((-5 [] -1) - (4 - -10)) ; ((5 ; -2) ; (7 & 4))) + (((4 ; -4) : (8 + 5)) + ((9 - -9) - (7 - -5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-902"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(b + a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a * a) & b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) & a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 >< b) & a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((1 >< 4) + -9) >< -3) * -5) * -7) - 1) - 9) ; 3) ; -9) * 7) - 2) >< 4) + 5) * -1) [] 8) [] 9) & -9) ; -4)\nLet B = ((((-1 [] -1) & (5 & -4)) - ((3 * 6) + (-2 + 8))) & (((-1 ; 2) + (9 * 7)) + ((4 + -7) - (3 * -6))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((-5 ; 6) >< 7) ; 1) - 2) & -7) * 5) [] 6) ; 3) ; 5) ; 5) & 7) * -6) * -3) + -8) [] -4) ; -4) + 10).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-1510"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((-5 ; 5) <> (-3 + 10)) ; ((6 # -4) * (-7 - -5))) <> (((-2 # 3) ! (1 + 2)) ; ((-3 * -3) <> (-10 + -3))))\nLet B = ((((-4 + 2) * (-8 - -7)) ! ((3 * 6) - (1 * -5))) ; (((7 ! -7) # (-2 <> 4)) ; ((-3 <> -9) ; (6 # -6))))\nLet C = ((((-4 * -9) - (10 ; -9)) + ((-1 + -9) + (-9 <> -3))) <> (((8 * -6) ! (-9 ; 2)) + ((-8 ; 8) - (-6 ; -9)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-2794"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b - a) @ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) @ a$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a @ b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a @ b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a @ -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((9 >< 9) ~ (-9 @ 2)) - ((2 [] 5) + (-5 * -4))) [] (((3 + 8) >< (-2 @ -1)) @ ((4 @ 6) ~ (10 - 3))))\nLet B = (((((((((((-3 >< 9) ~ 8) @ -10) @ 8) + 1) + -2) * 6) [] 5) ~ -2) + -8) [] 7)\nLet C = ((((-1 * 8) @ (10 ~ 2)) + ((-8 >< -6) [] (9 >< 3))) ~ (((-5 [] -5) - (-10 [] 9)) + ((2 - 7) >< (-4 + -9)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "57548"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(a - a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(b # a) ][ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a # b) ][ a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-6 >< -1) ][ (-1 @ 9)) + ((10 ][ -6) # (5 @ -7))) >< (((9 + 6) >< (3 @ -2)) ][ ((2 - 7) @ (1 ][ -2))))\nLet B = ((((3 # 8) @ (3 + -2)) >< ((6 >< 8) - (10 ][ 2))) + (((10 @ -1) # (-6 - 9)) @ ((3 - -9) >< (1 >< -5))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((-4 >< -10) ][ 2) ][ -9) >< 6) - 9) + 5) - 6) - -7) - 6) ][ 3) * 3) @ -2) + -7) + 4) + 10) ][ -7).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(2 * b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a ! a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ! b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((-9 ! -7) - (7 ][ 4)) + ((-9 ! -6) ][ (10 * 1))) ][ (((5 & -4) ][ (9 - 7)) + ((-10 - -7) ][ (5 ! 1))))\nLet B = ((((8 ! -5) + (-9 ! 5)) * ((-9 - 1) & (-8 & -8))) ][ (((8 * 8) <> (-6 & -2)) ! ((-2 - 7) + (9 * 9))))\nLet C = ((((4 & 8) - (-3 * -3)) ][ ((1 * 4) <> (-5 & 6))) & (((-6 & 4) & (10 - -2)) - ((-10 - 4) ! (-9 & -8)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a ][ b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ][ -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((3 ! 4) + (3 * 7)) + ((-10 ! 10) + (-2 ][ -8))) ! (((-7 [] 1) ! (-1 ~ -2)) + ((-9 ][ -2) ][ (-5 + 3))))\nLet B = ((((1 * -7) - (6 ~ 9)) ~ ((-2 * 7) * (-7 ! 7))) * (((-8 * -5) [] (3 ][ -8)) [] ((-6 [] -10) - (7 ][ 6))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((8 + -1) * -5) + 9) ][ -4) - -4) ! 1) * 6) ~ 8) + 10) ][ 2) ][ 10) * 6) ~ -6) ~ 4) ! 5) ][ 10) ! -8).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "646"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(b + a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 - b) # a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a @ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((1 - 9) & (6 # 3)) - ((9 ! -4) & (-4 # -9))) * (((4 + -4) # (4 @ 10)) @ ((4 # -7) - (-9 ! -6))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((5 & -2) # -9) # 1) * 3) # -1) & 2) * -3) * -7) ! -9) * 1) @ 8) - 1) @ -5) & 5)\nLet C = ((((-2 - 9) * (10 # 4)) * ((-2 - -9) @ (-1 @ -9))) - (((-10 # -9) & (6 + -6)) # ((-4 & 6) # (-3 ! 4)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "1848"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $(a * a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(2 : b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $a : b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((6 * -4) ! (10 : 9)) + ((-9 - 4) * (9 * 4))) ~ (((5 - 4) >< (-4 >< -6)) : ((9 ~ -3) ~ (-7 * 1))))\nLet B = ((((-3 * 6) >< (10 >< -6)) - ((4 * 9) * (7 ~ 9))) + (((2 >< -7) ! (8 - -2)) >< ((5 ! -2) ~ (8 : -5))))\nLet C = ((((8 ~ -3) : (6 + -5)) ~ ((8 ! -4) ! (9 ! -10))) : (((10 - 5) * (-2 - 3)) + ((-2 >< -6) + (7 ! -9)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-55224"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a * a) & b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) & a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a & b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((-2 : 10) ~ 10) + -9) & -5) ~ -1) - 10) ~ -9) & 7) - 1) - -10) <> -1) + -10) & -9) <> -10)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((2 & -10) + -3) & -4) - 3) + -7) - -2) : 3) ~ -10) ~ -9) ~ -4) <> 1) * 4) : 8) + -9) - 8)\nLet C = ((((-6 : 2) <> (8 - -6)) : ((8 <> 6) ~ (8 + 3))) - (((2 & -9) & (-3 - -4)) - ((-1 ~ -10) + (-10 - 1)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "4043"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b - a) ! b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) ! a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $a [] b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((7 - 8) * (-6 + -3)) * ((3 @ -7) # (-9 * -1))) # (((5 @ -9) # (10 # 5)) [] ((-2 - -3) - (9 [] -8))))\nLet B = ((((-6 @ -4) - (9 ! 10)) - ((-4 + -5) ! (10 - -9))) # (((5 - -5) [] (4 * -5)) - ((9 - -9) [] (6 ! -4))))\nLet C = (((((((((((4 @ 9) + 10) [] -7) @ -4) * 9) + -3) # 7) * 5) [] 6) # 4) - -2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-85"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ; b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a : a) ; b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b : b) ; a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a : b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((2 + 4) : -10) ; 5) ; 6) + -1) @ 6) + -5) * -1) @ 6) @ 8) + -6) [] 9) ; -3)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((((-2 * -6) : -2) @ -8) : 5) ; 3) * -1) : -2) * 2) @ -4) [] -8) @ 7) - 8) ; 1) [] -3) @ -9) * -1) : 9) [] 2) : -8) @ 8) [] -1)\nLet C = ((((1 : -10) [] (-7 * 4)) @ ((9 : 10) - (-8 + -10))) + (((-8 * 6) : (1 : 2)) @ ((-8 - -8) * (-5 [] -9)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-788"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a * a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 ~ b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((-9 - -6) ; 10) ; -5) * -9) ~ -3) ! -8) ; -7) ~ 2) ! 4) ~ 8) ~ 5) - 7) & -4) - -6)\nLet B = ((((((((((((3 - 4) # 3) * -5) ! -3) & 2) ; -6) + 3) ! 2) - -8) ! -10) ! 7) * -10)\nLet C = ((((4 - 4) - (-7 ; 10)) * ((2 - 6) ~ (4 # -3))) - (((4 ~ 9) # (4 # -1)) & ((-2 - 5) & (-2 ; -8)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "84322"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a + a) ! b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) ! a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $a >< b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((-3 + 1) >< (3 * -2)) >< ((6 + -4) - (-9 - -6))) ! (((-9 * -10) & (3 ! 9)) >< ((-3 ! 7) * (10 - -1))))\nLet B = ((((8 - -2) ! (1 ! 7)) : ((9 * 4) : (-6 >< -10))) + (((1 >< -8) * (6 : 2)) & ((3 - 5) - (-9 - 6))))\nLet C = ((((-1 & 7) ! (2 >< 8)) * ((-10 - -7) : (-9 & -8))) ! (((-4 & 9) >< (1 ! -5)) : ((-4 & 9) : (-8 : 10)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "13486"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $(b + a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) - a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((-7 & -7) ][ (-3 ][ -9)) >< ((-10 * 1) * (5 - 2))) - (((-9 ][ -2) * (1 * 1)) + ((2 ! -2) ! (3 >< 10))))\nLet B = ((((3 - -4) ][ (-5 >< -6)) >< ((2 - -2) >< (-4 & -8))) ][ (((8 ! 2) ][ (-9 - -1)) & ((-7 ! -9) ][ (-7 ][ 2))))\nLet C = ((((-2 ! 1) ! (-5 + -9)) ][ ((-8 * -6) >< (-8 + -2))) - (((-9 * -10) * (-6 - 2)) ! ((-3 ][ 1) * (-3 >< 4)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-325"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a ! b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ! -b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ~ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((9 ! -9) ! (-1 * 5)) * ((-9 * 4) ! (-8 : 2))) + (((10 ~ 4) : (7 + -4)) * ((-5 : 5) ~ (-1 ~ 3))))\nLet B = ((((6 ~ -9) + (-6 ~ 4)) + ((-5 ][ 1) + (-9 - -3))) + (((6 ! 5) ~ (-9 ][ 7)) - ((-3 - -1) - (2 + -7))))\nLet C = ((((7 ! 9) ~ (10 * 6)) - ((-6 ][ 6) : (-8 + -8))) : (((-3 ! -9) ! (-6 + 3)) ! ((2 - -1) : (3 ! -2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-3084"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 ! b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((4 + -2) ! -5) + 5) + -7) * 4) @ 6) - 2) * -8) - -6) * -10) + -3) [] 6) + 10)\nLet B = ((((((((((((-2 ! 5) + 9) @ 5) ! 2) - -7) * -9) - 5) - 9) + -4) + -3) @ -9) & -3)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((((2 & -9) * 10) * 10) @ -6) @ 1) * 5) & -10) * -9) ! -4) ! -8) ! -1) [] -4) & -1) [] -3) @ -6) [] 4) & 7) ! 10) @ 4) * -3) * 9) ! 9) & 3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-9390"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $(2 + b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a >< b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((8 + -9) [] (4 - -2)) + ((1 >< -10) + (-10 [] -7))) - (((-2 ~ 7) + (1 - -5)) >< ((-4 * 3) ~ (9 - -3))))\nLet B = (((((((((((3 ~ 7) - -4) ; 6) + 7) - 1) * 2) [] 7) - -5) [] 6) * 8) [] -1)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((((-10 - -5) + -10) * -10) - -10) ~ 9) [] -3) ~ 9) + -3) - -3) ; 10) [] 10) [] -10) + 3) >< 10) * 8) ~ -4) >< -8) - -5) [] 9) [] -10) + 10) ~ 9) >< -7).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-59"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a [] b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - a) [] b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) [] a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $a @ b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((3 @ 6) @ -9) # -1) - -1) : -1) : -10) [] -1) # -9) @ -9) @ -9) * -5) @ 1) - 2) : -8) [] -1) [] -9) # 10) : 1) * 3)\nLet B = ((((-8 * -3) # (1 # -8)) - ((2 * -8) @ (-5 * 9))) [] (((1 + 7) # (-6 [] -6)) : ((2 # -7) - (9 * -5))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((5 + 3) [] -6) + 2) # -8) [] -4) # -3) @ -6) * 7) : -7) # 4) : 10) * 4) * 9).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-127"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a * a) @ b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) @ a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a >< b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a @ b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-6 * -3) >< (4 * -1)) + ((-8 * -9) ; (-4 & 10))) & (((-7 + -1) & (-4 * -6)) @ ((-2 + 5) ; (3 ; -5))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((((7 - 6) & 7) + -5) + -5) >< 3) @ 8) + 8) >< 7) ; -5) @ -3) - -10) * -5) - 4) + -6) @ 9) ; -10) + 4) @ 1)\nLet C = ((((-5 * -7) * (10 @ 2)) + ((2 >< -5) & (-9 >< 2))) @ (((4 & -4) & (4 * 1)) >< ((-10 - -5) - (-4 - 3)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-16869"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a * a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(2 [] b) ; a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ; b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((6 * 10) [] (6 + 10)) [] ((-2 # -9) * (-6 ; 4))) : (((-2 : -7) * (5 [] 1)) - ((4 : -9) ; (-4 & -4))))\nLet B = ((((4 - -1) ; (9 - 10)) - ((6 [] 9) [] (2 + -7))) # (((4 : 8) - (1 : -4)) * ((-4 [] -6) # (5 [] -9))))\nLet C = ((((-2 * -8) + (-6 : 7)) * ((-6 & -1) : (1 : -2))) # (((6 & 1) : (2 [] -1)) : ((-9 [] 1) - (-8 : 10)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-1702"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b : a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a : b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a ! a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ! b) * a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((7 ][ 1) [] (-8 ][ 4)) ][ ((10 - -1) : (4 ][ -7))) + (((-8 ~ -5) + (-8 ! -10)) ~ ((-3 * 2) * (6 [] -5))))\nLet B = (((((((((((5 ~ -7) ][ -6) - -9) ! -10) + -8) : 2) * 4) ! -10) * 5) - -4) : -5)\nLet C = ((((((((((((-7 ~ -2) [] 8) ][ -5) + -10) + -1) : -6) ! -2) ! 3) ! -1) + -4) * 7) ~ -9).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-1144"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $a [] b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((7 ][ -8) @ (9 @ -9)) - ((3 * -7) * (3 - -5))) * (((-4 * -2) [] (-8 ][ 6)) ; ((7 @ -7) [] (8 + -4))))\nLet B = ((((-3 * -10) ; (-9 + 5)) [] ((-2 @ -2) + (7 ][ -7))) ][ (((-9 + 4) * (-2 * -8)) - ((-5 [] -5) [] (5 * -3))))\nLet C = ((((4 * -8) @ (6 ][ 1)) ][ ((-2 + 1) - (9 [] 2))) [] (((-2 [] 1) ][ (4 + -7)) [] ((8 [] 3) [] (8 - 9)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "2267"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 * b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-1 <> 3) @ (-2 + 10)) ][ ((-9 * 7) >< (5 - 6))) <> (((-3 >< -9) ][ (1 @ -8)) <> ((-6 ][ -6) @ (3 ][ -10))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((((((-10 + -3) @ 7) + -3) + 1) * 8) - 1) <> 4) <> 10) * -4) - 5) ][ 6) - -1) >< -10) @ 3) ][ 6) ][ -3) * -7) @ -6) - -3) >< -6) >< 8) ][ 5) - 10)\nLet C = (((((((((((((5 * 5) - 8) >< -9) ][ -8) @ 3) - 9) + 9) * 2) - 2) <> -5) + 1) - 2) ][ -3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "265"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b + a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) * a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((4 # -5) @ -8) - 3) ][ 5) + 8) @ 10) : 8) @ -8) ][ 6) @ -2) + -2) * -9) + 5) ][ 1) - 4) * -5) - -5) # -8) - -10) # 1) @ -10)\nLet B = ((((-3 - 3) * (-8 : 3)) + ((-4 ][ -3) : (1 - -5))) - (((1 * 8) ][ (-6 - 3)) @ ((-6 - -3) : (-7 # 9))))\nLet C = ((((-2 : -8) - (8 : 6)) ][ ((-10 - -6) : (-6 # 4))) : (((4 - 4) - (-7 @ 3)) ][ ((-10 - -3) * (-1 @ 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-992"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 * b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $a : b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b ; a) : b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a ; b) : a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((-5 : 6) : -1) - 8) - 1) ; 2) ! 10) - -9) ; -2) ! 2) ! -7) ! -6) + 10) + 2) - 2) - -6) - 3) [] 1) : -10) - 7)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((-1 ; 1) ; 4) * 4) * 4) ! -4) - 2) - 6) [] 4) ; -5) + 1) + -6) : 9) ; 7) [] -8) * -10) * -3)\nLet C = ((((((((((((-4 ; -3) - 3) : 2) ; -2) - -7) - 9) [] -7) ! 1) + 9) ! -7) ! -1) [] -4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "191"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b @ a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a @ b) - a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((-5 + -10) * 6) * -5) + -2) >< -4) * 6) >< -2) ][ 2) - -10) * -7) ][ 2) <> -7) ][ 6)\nLet B = ((((-5 ][ 2) * (-4 * -8)) >< ((9 + -9) <> (2 <> -8))) * (((-2 + 2) * (2 * 8)) * ((6 ][ -5) + (-5 <> -6))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((-7 + 5) - -2) - 7) ][ 9) <> -7) ][ -6) <> 6) >< 8) - 5) - -2) * -9) - -7) >< -8) + -4) + 10) @ 8) * 4) <> 5) @ 4) - -1).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-136"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a [] a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b [] b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a [] b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $a & b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((6 [] -2) - (7 * -6)) * ((-3 - -2) * (5 @ 10))) [] (((-5 + 8) @ (3 - 2)) ; ((2 @ 8) & (8 & -8))))\nLet B = ((((4 + -7) + (-7 [] 1)) ; ((-4 @ 9) * (7 @ -5))) + (((3 & -1) & (-2 @ -5)) [] ((1 - 2) [] (-2 - 7))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((((3 & 6) ; 6) * 7) ; -4) @ 7) - -4) + -6) [] -8) + 4) - -6) @ -10) * 9) + 6) ; -2) - -7) ; -3) + 3) @ -9) & -1) & 7) * 2) [] 4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "18953"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a + a) [] b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) [] a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((-9 * -4) * (-4 + -8)) * ((-7 [] 3) + (8 * -6))) >< (((-8 - 4) * (2 [] -5)) >< ((3 - 3) @ (2 ! 6))))\nLet B = ((((3 [] -5) - (-7 - -5)) + ((1 * 10) [] (-6 * -4))) >< (((7 + -3) ! (3 * 10)) ! ((-7 + 4) - (-1 >< -9))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((((-10 @ 9) ! 8) - 1) ! -10) @ 3) + 3) + 3) - -4) ! 7) ! 10) [] -8) >< -9) >< 10) + -9) * -5) ! 3) @ 8) @ 8) >< -6) [] 10) [] 4) ! 4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(2 + b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a : b$.\n\nLet A = ((((10 * -9) : (6 * -9)) + ((6 + 7) # (9 & 1))) * (((-6 : 1) * (-2 @ -1)) * ((7 <> -2) + (4 * -5))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((1 <> 1) : -8) # -8) # 4) <> 8) @ -9) + 4) & 1) & -1) & -10) # -5) <> 2) - -7) @ -7) * -3)\nLet C = ((((-10 + -1) @ (8 & 8)) # ((-7 @ -10) # (5 @ -9))) # (((5 + -10) & (-1 + 6)) : ((-6 * -1) @ (-1 <> -5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-314"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a + a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a <> b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a ~ b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((-9 >< 4) * 7) # -8) <> 5) @ -3) ~ 1) >< 9) * -10) * -7) + -6) * 6) - -7) >< -4) * -1) - -2) <> 5)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((10 + 1) - -3) @ 8) @ -6) <> 4) <> -6) + -9) <> -10) + 8) ~ 3) + 6) # 1) - 7) <> 1) + -5) * -6) <> 4)\nLet C = (((((((((((((-5 ~ 5) >< -4) >< -1) >< 1) ~ -4) ~ -8) * 3) ~ 1) <> 8) # -7) - -8) # 4) ~ 2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-5742"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b + a) : b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((-6 * 7) ; -2) : 3) * -3) + -6) @ -7) - 3) + 2) + -7) ; -6) ; 7) ][ 4) * -1) + -6)\nLet B = ((((7 + 9) ; (8 ][ -10)) : ((-5 * 2) @ (7 + 1))) @ (((4 @ 2) : (9 ][ -8)) @ ((9 : 3) ][ (10 @ 4))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((-1 ; 4) * -9) ][ 10) + -8) + 2) @ -6) + 4) + 5) ; 2) - 4) - 2) + 1) - 4) : -10) @ 4) @ -3) * 7) + -5) : 3) : -4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-545"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((7 <> 6) + (8 : -8)) >< ((-7 & 9) <> (-2 - -7))) + (((4 >< -1) : (-10 * 2)) + ((-7 & 2) - (8 + 9))))\nLet B = ((((-4 & -8) >< (8 [] -3)) - ((7 * -3) * (5 * -6))) >< (((3 : 7) - (8 - -3)) * ((5 * 8) * (-8 - 10))))\nLet C = ((((9 * 1) : (5 + -3)) + ((-2 [] -5) >< (-10 + -5))) + (((9 : -9) <> (6 [] 8)) + ((-3 <> 1) [] (-6 >< -2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-11528"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 - b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b @ a) # b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a @ b) # a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a >< b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a @ b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-3 # -6) >< (-3 @ -9)) * ((-6 - -9) - (8 >< -4))) * (((-7 - 3) + (10 + 9)) [] ((9 @ -8) * (3 - -9))))\nLet B = ((((9 @ -9) + (2 >< -2)) + ((-7 + 10) - (-10 >< 9))) [] (((3 >< -10) # (6 [] 8)) ~ ((6 >< 2) - (-5 - -10))))\nLet C = (((((((((((3 # -7) @ -5) [] 7) # -6) >< -6) * -2) @ -1) - -4) @ 3) - 4) [] -8).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a + a) ! b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) ! a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((-6 & -7) ! -1) - 4) ! -7) + -4) ! 2) ! 4) : 1) & -3) ! -3) + -8) + 8) ; -10) ! -10) - -10) ! 9) : -4) + -7)\nLet B = ((((-1 + -3) ; (-10 - 2)) ; ((-4 + -8) + (-10 - 6))) - (((7 * -8) & (10 * -4)) - ((8 ! -5) - (-2 * 2))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((((-9 : 1) ; 7) : 7) ! 3) ! -8) ; -7) ; 9) ; 7) ! 9) ; 1) ; 1) * -7) & 10) * 7) * 3) ! 10) * 5) * 4) + 6) * -9) ! -9) : -7) & 4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a - a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(b & a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a & b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a : b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a : -b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((2 * -9) * -3) : -5) : 5) * 2) & -7) & 8) ! -2) : -6) + -6) & -3) * -9) & -6) : 7) >< -9)\nLet B = ((((-9 + -10) * (3 * -4)) [] ((6 * -6) ! (-10 : -1))) : (((5 : -10) ! (7 - -3)) - ((-4 - -9) >< (1 >< 3))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((10 ! -9) * -2) & 10) [] 4) : -5) [] -2) [] 4) + -10) * -4) + 1) [] -4) & 2) >< 3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "196"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a * a) [] b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) [] a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 <> b) [] a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b * a) [] b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) [] a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((9 & -4) * -4) - 8) ][ 9) * -1) >< 9) * 2) * 2) + 4) <> 2) >< 8) - -9) [] -6) >< -4) >< 9)\nLet B = ((((-3 * -10) & (1 ][ -10)) [] ((-5 [] 5) <> (-6 * 9))) >< (((4 ][ -8) [] (1 <> 7)) & ((-1 >< 3) ][ (1 + 5))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((7 <> -9) - -3) * 9) + 9) - 10) + -9) [] 2) & 2) >< 10) * -8) <> 5) + 9).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-76"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(b - a) ~ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) ~ a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a + a) ! b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) ! a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a ~ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((7 * -4) + (-5 ; 8)) ~ ((5 + -3) - (10 ! -2))) >< (((-2 ~ -5) & (-7 + 8)) >< ((3 ~ 8) ~ (-10 ; 2))))\nLet B = ((((-3 * -8) - (-7 * -2)) >< ((1 + -4) ; (-9 ~ -6))) & (((-5 * 1) ! (-4 * -4)) * ((-9 ~ 5) ! (-9 >< 5))))\nLet C = ((((10 ~ -7) - (7 & 3)) >< ((8 ~ -3) - (1 + 3))) + (((-6 ~ -6) ; (-9 ! 4)) ; ((5 ~ 1) >< (-10 & 3)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 + b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $a # b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((1 ; 3) * -7) : -4) * 10) ][ -10) # -1) ; -1) : 4) : 9) : -9) + -2) # 9) * -6)\nLet B = ((((-4 ; -9) ][ (10 - 8)) * ((-5 + 5) + (-4 : -8))) - (((-4 + 8) + (3 ][ 2)) - ((-7 ! 4) + (-3 : 6))))\nLet C = ((((10 + 8) * (-3 * -10)) ; ((-3 ][ -6) + (-10 ][ 5))) ; (((3 - -3) ; (1 # -2)) ][ ((-2 + -10) + (-1 ! -3)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-1799"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a [] b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((-7 + -6) >< -9) ][ 9) @ 1) @ -9) >< -4) [] 7) ][ 5) ][ 8) >< -7) [] 8) >< 10)\nLet B = ((((4 + -7) + (1 [] -5)) + ((-8 >< -1) ][ (2 [] 2))) : (((1 >< 1) >< (10 ][ -2)) - ((-10 ][ -10) * (-5 + -4))))\nLet C = ((((9 + 10) + (-4 [] -5)) ][ ((6 @ -3) [] (6 @ 9))) + (((-3 ][ -5) * (-6 [] -4)) + ((8 @ -2) [] (-7 [] -7)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-1082"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b * a) <> b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) <> a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $a <> b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((10 - 4) - 5) <> 4) + -4) [] -6) <> 3) <> 1) [] 6) ~ 10) * -1) <> -9) <> -4) + -8) [] -4) - 5) [] -9) - -6)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((((-7 * 6) <> -10) ~ 10) * 8) ~ -2) [] -8) - 5) * 1) + -5) <> 9) * -1) ][ 5) <> -2) [] 3) ][ 10) + -8) [] 5) <> -4) * 4) * -1) [] 5)\nLet C = ((((-10 <> 9) ][ (-5 ][ -8)) ][ ((10 [] 10) <> (10 [] 2))) - (((-1 ~ -6) + (10 ][ 6)) + ((1 ~ -6) [] (-5 * -4)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-652"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(a - a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 >< b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((5 # 1) - -3) - -1) & 7) * -5) <> -2) # 9) [] 5) + 6) [] -9) # 4)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((-6 + -10) * 1) - 2) <> 3) + -3) * -6) & 3) + -5) <> 6) + 9) + -6) <> 3) * -2) # -7) <> 9) # -6)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((1 + -7) # -3) * 1) + 1) & -2) <> 8) # -3) + 1) * 8) >< 9) # -1) # 6) >< -6) >< 8) - 3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 * b) <> a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b + a) ; b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) ; a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((-1 ~ 5) <> 6) ~ -2) - 8) - -7) # -6) ! -5) ~ -8) # -2) * 7) # -8) - -1) <> 5) ~ -7) * -2) - -1) - -6) ~ -6) - 8)\nLet B = ((((9 + 7) ! (-1 <> -9)) - ((3 + 5) * (-4 ~ -6))) <> (((3 ; -10) ~ (-2 <> -5)) # ((-1 + 3) ~ (-7 * -5))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((2 # 8) ~ -2) * -8) ~ 4) ; 6) ! -2) ! 9) - -7) # -5) + 5) # 1) + -2) # -1) - -6) <> -10) ~ 6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((3 >< 6) + 7) + 4) ~ 6) ; 7) - 1) - 2) ; 4) ~ 2) ; -3) + 8) ~ 3) - -9) * 8) & -1) + -8) - 10) ~ -3) ~ -7)\nLet B = (((((((((((((-7 ; -7) + 6) - 9) ~ 2) - 9) * 3) - -10) ~ -10) + -3) ; -1) * 7) ; 3) - 9)\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((((-1 & 4) >< -10) * -4) - -7) + -3) + 3) >< -2) * -9) * 2) ; 10) - -2) + -8) + -5) ; -4) ; 9) >< 5) - 2) >< -6) ~ 4) & 6) - -9) ; 6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a ~ a) : b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ~ b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a : b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(b : a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a : b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((6 - 9) <> -6) : 4) + -10) <> 7) ! 7) <> -6) <> 7) <> 7) ][ 7) ! 3) - 3)\nLet B = ((((10 ! 3) - (-10 ][ -6)) ][ ((-2 * 10) - (5 ~ 1))) - (((-10 * 9) ! (-10 : -5)) * ((-1 * 10) : (4 ! -8))))\nLet C = ((((5 <> -10) + (-5 + 7)) + ((-9 * 4) : (7 <> -3))) - (((-4 ][ -6) - (-2 * -3)) <> ((5 : -1) * (2 ~ -5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-72098"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a ~ b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 ~ b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((1 @ 6) :*- (7 :: 3)) -~ ((-2 : -6) +-+ (-5 :!! 3))) ~*- (((10 ~@@ 8) !@~ (5 * 7)) -@~ ((-2 ~~ 2) - (-9 @~ -5))))\nLet B = ((((7 *+@ -3) !:* (-10 ~-- -1)) :@ ((4 !@ 7) !+ (-9 *:! 7))) - (((-6 !~ -4) @:@ (1 ** 6)) -! ((6 - -6) ! (-9 ~- 6))))\nLet C = (((((((((((6 : -9) !*: 2) ~ 5) @~ 1) -@@ 7) ~ 10) !@ -2) +!@ 5) :!! -9) @@ 8) :!! -3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-58396"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(b - a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a # b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(a [] b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a [] -b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((-5 <> -8) <> -7) # 7) # 5) * -1) - -3) [] -1) <> 4) : -9) [] -5) # 3) * -5) + -7) <> 4) : 8) * 4) + -5)\nLet B = ((((-1 : -8) + (-4 [] -5)) [] ((-2 : -7) & (4 : 3))) * (((1 <> 9) * (-10 [] -10)) : ((-1 * -9) & (10 # -6))))\nLet C = ((((-1 * -7) # (9 * 9)) + ((-6 + -2) [] (9 # -9))) : (((-2 [] 10) + (2 # -6)) * ((10 : 4) <> (5 * -1)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "128369"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a + a) : b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b <> a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a <> b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(2 + b) ~ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((4 [] -2) * (3 <> -7)) * ((7 # -1) - (-1 : -8))) [] (((-10 <> 9) # (2 * 4)) + ((-1 [] 9) <> (7 [] 10))))\nLet B = ((((-9 * -8) + (8 * 8)) - ((-8 ~ 1) # (8 * -9))) - (((-5 + -2) [] (5 + 4)) # ((10 + -3) <> (-5 + 7))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((((-6 : 4) <> 6) * 8) : 2) # 7) ~ -6) - -2) * 5) ~ 5) + 5) * -8) [] 9) * -6) <> 1) - 9) * 2) ~ -6) ~ -5) : -1) [] 5) * -1) - 6) * -9).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-3147"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 [] b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(b * a) ; b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) ; a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((7 + -1) * 5) # 9) + 9) # 5) # 5) ~ 7) ! 9) # 3) + -8) ; -8) ; 9) [] 8) ; 7) + -4) ! 2) + 8) ~ -10) ! 4) ; -8) ~ -2)\nLet B = (((((((((((((-9 # -9) ! -5) * 4) ; -6) ! 9) ! -3) ! -10) ~ 8) ; 8) - 1) ; 6) - -2) ; -6)\nLet C = ((((7 * -3) # (1 - 10)) ~ ((2 # 3) - (-5 # -3))) * (((5 + -8) - (-6 * 3)) ! ((4 ! 10) - (-4 * -3)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-19743"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 # b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ][ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(b : a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a : b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((-8 ! -10) - 7) ][ -10) ][ 1) ][ 7) ][ -10) ! 10) ][ -4) + 6) ; 5) - 1) ; -6) ][ 3) : -6) : 2) # -1) ][ -4) ; 7) + -2) + 4) : -2)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((3 + 4) # -6) ; -5) - -10) + 8) - -9) ][ -9) # -4) * -2) * 2) ; -4) * -8) : -3) * -6) - -4) # -6) * -6)\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((8 - 5) ! -1) - -9) ][ 1) + -6) ; -8) ! -9) - 6) - 2) + -6) ! -8) : -1) ; 7) : 7) + -4) + 6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-6132"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(a - a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a # b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a # -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 * b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a [] b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b ; a) [] b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a ; b) [] a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((10 - -6) - -9) >< -5) ; 8) >< -1) & 10) & 4) ; 8) >< 7) >< -7) # -7)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((-5 + -8) & 4) ; -8) [] -3) + -1) & 6) * -6) [] 2) # -7) * -5) [] 1) >< 6) + 10) ][ -5)\nLet C = ((((1 ][ 8) # (6 + 4)) * ((5 [] 4) + (5 - 8))) * (((4 + -1) ; (-2 [] 4)) ; ((7 ; 9) >< (5 & 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(2 >< b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a >< b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $a [] b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a : b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a ; b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((2 ! 9) >< -2) - -9) [] 9) + 2) ! 2) - -6) + -7) [] -1) * 8) : 7) : -6) : -10)\nLet B = ((((1 : -7) >< (8 ; 10)) ! ((5 + 8) - (8 >< 4))) * (((6 : 9) [] (8 - -7)) : ((-8 - -2) [] (6 - 8))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((((-5 : -3) ; -2) : 5) + 4) - 10) + 5) ; -10) >< -7) [] 8) + 6) ; 4) + -3) >< 6) - -5) [] -8) - 8) - 1) ! 4) - -9) + -5) >< 4) : -9) : 1).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "61540"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a <> b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a <> b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b + a) <> b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) <> a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((10 + 8) - (5 - -8)) - ((6 ][ -5) - (-5 - 6))) + (((-9 [] 3) ][ (1 ~ 6)) <> ((-10 * 2) ~ (1 <> -2))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((-9 : 10) [] 7) <> 2) : 3) <> -4) ~ 7) ~ 2) : 5) ~ 5) - 9) ][ 9) : 6) <> -8) * -8)\nLet C = ((((2 : 6) <> (3 - -4)) <> ((6 ~ 5) * (2 ~ 8))) - (((4 + -3) <> (9 : -6)) <> ((-4 + -9) + (5 - -5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(b + a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a # b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a + a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) - a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((9 : 3) ][ (-7 & -5)) # ((-6 # 4) + (-1 # 10))) ; (((-3 : -4) & (-7 : 6)) - ((5 # 4) ][ (-7 * -6))))\nLet B = ((((-6 - -2) & (2 - -3)) ; ((4 & 7) * (1 * 4))) # (((-1 ; 3) ][ (-5 ][ 5)) # ((9 ; -6) : (4 - 8))))\nLet C = ((((5 ][ 5) * (1 ][ 3)) : ((-8 & 4) & (-8 : 5))) & (((-2 - 1) # (-6 ][ 8)) # ((-7 * -6) & (-6 ][ 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-38"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a & b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 + b) & a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((((3 ; -3) ; 7) ! -1) + 5) & -5) ; -10) & -9) ; -6) [] -5) ! 4) + -6) [] -5) * -4) & -2) ; -8) ][ 5) ; -1) + -8) - -1) ! -2)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((-3 & 7) - -9) ; -7) + 2) & -9) ; -9) ! 4) - -7) & 8) * 9) & 10) & 9) * 5) & 2) * -2)\nLet C = (((((((((((((-9 - -5) ][ 5) * 3) & -4) [] -7) [] -6) ! -4) ][ -2) & 7) + -5) [] 10) ! -1) & 6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a ~ b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a ~ b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ~ -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-7 ~ 2) - (8 # -7)) # ((-2 # 8) : (-6 # -9))) ~ (((2 + -3) ~ (10 + -2)) # ((-10 ; 4) - (5 # 6))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((-8 & -7) * -6) - 3) # -1) ~ -3) & 3) - 1) + -9) - -7) # 9) : 8) # 6) : 4) ; -7) : -2) - -1)\nLet C = ((((1 ; 4) * (8 ; 8)) ; ((-3 + -3) ~ (6 & -3))) : (((-7 - 10) : (-5 + 6)) - ((-6 ~ 2) ~ (10 - -4)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-6497"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(b [] a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a [] b) + a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((1 @*+ 4) <>+[] (-4 *<>* -1)) @; ((-1 <> 6) ; (2 ;* 1))) @@@ (((5 ;- 5) []@@ (-8 - 1)) ; ((2 +; -5) +[]- (3 - -8))))\nLet B = (((((((((((8 *; 8) + 10) -+ 9) +[] 7) +- 4) []<>[] 4) @@ 9) -+ 7) @ 3) ; -5) ;[] 3)\nLet C = ((((9 @+ -1) <> (-3 + -5)) [];- ((8 <><> -5) <>- (-9 <>* 3))) ; (((-4 <>@+ -5) ; (4 @; -9)) *+ ((-5 [];- 3) @[]+ (10 *+<> 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a * a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 + b) ~ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-2 ][ -7) ][ (-2 @ -7)) * ((9 - 1) ~ (2 - -8))) - (((2 - 2) @][ (-2 +: -8)) + ((-10 @ 2) :~~ (5 @ 8))))\nLet B = ((((-7 + -2) +- (4 : -1)) : ((1 ~:@ -2) @~ (-10 ~+- 1))) : (((-1 -~ -4) *-~ (-10 : -10)) ][ ((-4 ~@ 2) ][ (-2 ~@ 2))))\nLet C = ((((7 :+@ -10) ~ (10 ~ -5)) -][@ ((1 +:@ 7) *-* (-2 ][ 7))) - (((3 - -6) +* (-1 :- -8)) ][- ((-8 :-* -3) -+][ (9 ~@* -2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "27002"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a + a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a : b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a : b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a : -b$.\n$a # b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 @ b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((2 [] 5) & (1 # -2)) : ((-6 : -2) * (5 [] 7))) [] (((5 - -1) - (-4 - 2)) : ((6 ][ 8) [] (-1 & -7))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((9 [] 6) * 3) @ -8) @ 9) * -3) ][ 2) * 7) @ -1) ][ 1) * 4) @ -4) * -3) @ -1) [] -9) * -1) [] 3) ][ -7)\nLet C = ((((-2 : 10) + (3 + 6)) : ((4 + -7) & (4 + 2))) & (((9 + -9) @ (-8 * -1)) & ((-2 @ -10) @ (-1 ][ 6)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-10882"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 * b) # a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(b + a) # b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) # a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((-4 - 9) # -6) - 3) : -10) # -7) + 6) # -1) * -4) <> -5) - 1) & -1)\nLet B = ((((5 & 5) & (-1 + -3)) : ((1 * -9) ! (3 & 4))) <> (((-1 - -9) * (4 + -2)) # ((9 - -6) - (3 ! -9))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((((-10 + -6) - 4) - -1) * -1) * -9) # 1) - 4) # -6) # -10) # 3) & 10) - 3) ! -8) * -2) + 2) & 2) & -5) # -9) : -5) ! -6) ! 3) # 1) # -2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a ; a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ; b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(b # a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a # b) * a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((-4 ; -3) & -5) # 5) ! 6) & -3) &+ -3) ;*- 1) +- -1) ; -9) &! -9) ! 5) -; -1)\nLet B = ((((4 *+ 8) # (-10 ;; 1)) #;- ((6 - 7) &+! (-3 &; 7))) +! (((7 +; 8) -! (6 -- -4)) + ((-9 !-# 3) # (-6 -- 1))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((3 -;; 2) & -8) ; 9) *- -9) ++! 5) #+; -3) & -4) -- -5) +# -4) - 3) ! 9) !*; -1) &; 7).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a ][ b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ][ -b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a + a) ; b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) ; a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((-10 -* -1) ][~ 5) !!- -3) -* 1) ! 2) ++; 5) ~+! -5) ++][ 3) ][][ 10) ][* 4) +~ -2)\nLet B = ((((6 !- 8) +~ (-10 ; -1)) ; ((6 ; -1) +- (2 *- 5))) ;~- (((-3 + 1) *! (-6 ][; 1)) ][ ((-9 ;! 3) - (8 -~+ 4))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((-1 ~; -10) ! 9) ][+~ 6) ! 1) -- 6) ! -10) !*- -3) ][ -9) ! -3) ][ 6) ][ 1) ~ -6) * -3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-29"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a [] b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(b - a) @ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) @ a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((10 @ -5) - 5) - -1) - 4) <> 2) [] 4) <> -4) [] 7) : -9) + 10) * -3) @ -5)\nLet B = ((((-10 @ 4) ; (8 @ -5)) * ((-5 : -1) @ (10 <> 5))) ; (((6 ; -9) ; (5 & -9)) : ((-7 <> 3) <> (9 <> -5))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((6 + 1) ; -5) + -10) : -6) : 4) : 7) * -8) : 8) : -9) & 10) ; 6) : -1) : 10) + 10) + 2) [] -1) @ 2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "674"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a # b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b # a) ! b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a # b) ! a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((5 + 1) **+ 8) :+ 7) ! -3) [][] -4) : 1) + -1) +# -10) # -7) -* 2) :[] -7) *+ -3)\nLet B = ((((6 --+ -8) []!! (-6 !! -3)) - ((-1 *[] 4) ![]: (-4 #*- 6))) *#! (((-6 + -4) [][][] (10 + 5)) *#[] ((-2 !## -6) #! (-1 :-- -1))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((-10 ##[] -7) :[] 10) *+* -10) *- -2) []* -8) :-# 10) - 10) -+ 7) ! 8) #[]: -10) [] -3) *- 10) !# 8).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a # b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(2 - b) ~ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a * a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((4 - -5) : (6 ; -3)) # ((9 # -9) ! (-9 * 2))) * (((5 ~ -3) + (9 : -1)) : ((-2 - -4) ; (5 <> -1))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((-10 - 8) * -4) + 2) ; -9) <> 9) # -5) ~ 7) - -7) # 9) : -9) : 1) - 10) # 7) : -9) + 1)\nLet C = ((((-8 : 1) + (6 ; -10)) : ((-4 # -6) ~ (-2 + 7))) : (((-1 * 5) * (-9 ~ -9)) # ((6 * -10) + (-2 - -7)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "681"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(a * a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a >< b)$ if $a @ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a >< -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a @ b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a ! b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a @ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 ! b) >< a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((-7 ][ -3) ~ -3) + -4) ][ 9) - 9) <> -2) * -2) >< -4) <> -7) @ -10) @ -10) * -8)\nLet B = ((((-9 ][ -9) ][ (-10 + 2)) @ ((-9 >< 9) * (1 >< -3))) * (((8 ~ 8) >< (-5 ][ 2)) + ((9 @ -8) ][ (-1 * 8))))\nLet C = ((((9 @ -2) >< (-10 + -10)) - ((-5 - 10) + (9 ~ -5))) ][ (((4 * 4) >< (3 ][ -5)) ~ ((-2 + -7) >< (3 ! -8)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "4559"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 # b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(b & a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a & b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a & b)$ if $a ][ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a & -b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((((7 - 8) * 8) ][ -6) >< 3) ][ -8) * 2) * 5) & 6) [] -9) # -2) + 3) # 1) >< -10) # -7) >< -6) [] -5) >< 7) # 8) & -7) [] -9) [] 4) ][ 9) >< 10)\nLet B = ((((7 & 6) * (1 - -10)) + ((-1 >< -8) & (7 * 6))) - (((7 * -2) [] (10 ][ -2)) * ((6 + -9) & (5 & -4))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((-3 * 10) >< -6) - -5) [] -9) - -6) & 7) # -6) & 4) - 5) - -2) & 3) & -4) # 2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "172"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 + b) : a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a ; b)$ if $a ][ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ; -b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((-2 ; 3) <> -2) ! 3) <> -3) ! 1) + 7) * 10) - -3) ! 4) + -5) - 3) * -8) - 2) + 1) + -9) : 5) ; -4)\nLet B = ((((-1 : 9) + (-10 <> 7)) <> ((-1 * 3) * (-5 <> 2))) - (((3 ! -9) ! (-4 + -10)) - ((1 ; 7) <> (-7 <> -10))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((-7 - 6) ][ 1) ; 9) <> 9) ! -10) ! 10) * -7) ! 6) <> -8) ! -9) <> 9) * 3) <> -6) ; -7) ; 3) ][ 5) <> 10) ][ -2) + -4) ][ -3).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a >< a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b >< b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 >< b) @ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a <> b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a <> -b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((10 [] -2) - (7 [] 4)) @ ((-10 <> -2) * (6 * -10))) <> (((1 * 10) [] (-9 >< 3)) ~ ((-6 - 6) >< (9 [] -8))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((-10 ][ -10) <> -10) >< -6) @ -7) ][ -4) >< 1) <> 5) ][ -7) @ 3) * -4) <> -10) ][ 5) @ -9) - 10) - -3) @ 9) <> -6)\nLet C = (((((((((((((-7 <> 5) - -6) - -3) ][ -1) >< 7) ][ 2) ~ -1) <> -8) - 8) ~ -7) [] 1) @ 9) <> -10).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(2 - b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b * a) # b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) # a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a # a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b # b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a ][ b)$ if $a # b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ][ -b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((-1 & 6) ][ 7) ][ -5) # 1) ~ 6) [] 7) ][ 9) ~ -6) - -8) ! 9) ~ 5) ! 9) - -3) [] -5)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((-4 + -2) [] -1) - 6) [] 8) - 7) ][ -8) * -10) ][ 10) - 2) - -8) # -5) ][ 2) # -2) - -9) ][ -6) ! 5) & 10)\nLet C = ((((2 - -6) & (5 [] -10)) & ((1 - 3) # (6 ~ 7))) - (((-1 & 8) - (-5 & 3)) ][ ((8 ~ -2) ! (5 ][ 7)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "4198"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(a * a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((-10 *+ 9) <> 4) @ 6) ! -10) -!+ -2) @ -2) ><<>+ -6) -@>< -9) ><* 1) <>@ 5) +! -1) ! 8) -* 6) -><+ -3) ><@>< 3) +-+ 9) >< 4)\nLet B = ((((-3 @ -8) -<> (2 <> -6)) *-- ((-5 >< -1) -- (4 - 3))) ++ (((10 @ -3) *@+ (10 *@- 6)) ><>< ((-6 <>@<> 5) >< (7 *- -2))))\nLet C = ((((-3 +*+ 2) + (8 -* -10)) *- ((-9 ->< -3) @- (10 <>- -8))) !- (((-4 <> -6) @! (-1 **>< 9)) - ((2 @! 5) @<>! (7 !+ -1)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "40086"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 * b) # a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $a @ b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((8 @ 6) [] 1) +@* -9) @<>+ 10) *# -5) <>* -7) #* -2) + 8) *<>@ 2) #+ -4) +*- 7)\nLet B = ((((5 @ 3) #+# (-10 - -10)) +<>- ((-8 <>*- 9) - (-6 # -3))) *@+ (((-7 @[]- 5) @ (-2 *#+ 2)) -+ ((6 []+ -4) *@* (1 #- -7))))\nLet C = ((((-5 [] -7) <>* (-3 # -4)) #<>[] ((3 ** -7) # (3 #+[] 8))) * (((5 *@ -1) <>-[] (1 +* 7)) *@+ ((10 [] 4) +- (7 @<> -2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-51872"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a # b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 * b) ][ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((10 ~ 6) + 2) >< -1) <> 2) ][ 7) >< 4) >< -6) - 9) * 6) : 2) ~ 6)\nLet B = ((((((((((((5 - 6) - -10) + -6) <> -9) >< 7) ][ 5) * 8) ~ -1) <> 8) >< 8) # -6) ~ -2)\nLet C = ((((7 : 7) >< (-8 >< 9)) + ((4 * 3) + (8 <> -5))) # (((10 ][ -2) >< (-5 <> -2)) : ((9 >< -5) <> (9 + -1)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-287"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a + a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ~ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a : b$.\n\nLet A = ((((4 + 4) ! (7 # 8)) ~ ((5 ! 4) * (-7 : -6))) + (((8 >< 3) : (-3 - 3)) # ((-10 + -8) ! (-4 # -10))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((-4 # -6) ~ -7) - 2) >< -3) ~ 3) + 10) >< 4) + -6) + 9) * 2) * -9) ! -1) : 9) # 6) ~ 6) ! 6)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((2 - -5) : -3) ~ 7) + -1) >< 10) : -4) * -7) # 4) # -9) + 9) * -8) >< -9) ! 1) # -6) ~ -8) # -2) >< -3) + 3) ! 8) - -2) - 9).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-177"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(a + a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(b * a) # b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) # a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 # b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((-5 * -9) <> 10) + -8) @ -5) [] 6) @ 3) [] -8) <> -8) @ 2) >< -1) # -3) @ -4) ! -2)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((-2 # 3) - 4) - 8) @ 3) >< 10) @ -8) [] -7) @ -4) * 2) # -8) @ 5) [] 5) * 6) <> 4) @ -10)\nLet C = ((((8 * 3) <> (4 [] -4)) @ ((4 * -5) * (6 - -1))) >< (((10 <> 2) # (-6 >< 3)) * ((-3 # -2) * (-6 # 3)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-447"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 * b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a ][ b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ][ -b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a * a) ][ b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) ][ a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(b ~ a) ][ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a ~ b) ][ a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((((10 * 7) + 5) <> 8) ][ 10) >< 6) : -4) >< 2) + 6) ][ -7) ~ -7) ! -6) <> 7) >< -9) ][ -3) - -6) ][ 10) ~ 8) <> 4) >< -3) ! -4)\nLet B = ((((7 >< -1) ! (9 ! -1)) : ((-3 >< -10) - (7 >< -4))) + (((1 ! -8) >< (10 ][ 1)) ~ ((4 ~ -6) * (2 >< 8))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((7 ! 8) - 2) ! 10) >< 1) >< 3) ! -3) <> 7) - 8) >< 4) <> -6) ! 10) - -3) * 7).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-23310"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a @ a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b @ b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(2 <> b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a >< b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((4 * 5) * 6) ~ -10) : -7) + 2) >< -4) - -5) * 2) + 9) * -7) >< 2) >< -3) ~ 9)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((5 * -5) ~ -6) <> 10) * 2) - -9) ~ -1) + -7) <> -7) >< -5) @ 1) ! -10) >< 10) @ -8) - -10) <> -5) * -4)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((-5 >< -6) ~ -10) >< -6) - -10) + -10) + 7) - -3) >< -8) ~ 5) ~ 3) : -10) - 4) >< -10) - 10) * 9) ~ -4) <> -3) - 7) @ -1).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "70809"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(b - a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a ][ b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a & b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a & -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a & a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b & b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((-1 * -6) # -9) & -5) ][ -10) & -4) ][ 9) : 4) : -8) ][ -2) + -8) <> -9) + 6) & 1) - -8) - 10)\nLet B = ((((((((((((-7 - -2) * -8) ][ 9) * -5) # -8) & 5) ! -1) + -2) & -5) # 3) & -8) & 5)\nLet C = ((((-4 - -9) - (-3 * 3)) ][ ((3 <> -5) <> (-3 ][ -6))) + (((-8 ][ -3) & (-5 # -4)) ][ ((-8 <> 3) * (5 : -1)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "536"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a >< b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a >< b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a ~ a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ~ b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 * b) >< a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((3 * -7) [] (-9 * 5)) * ((-8 * 7) >< (2 - 4))) ][ (((10 + -5) * (9 * -2)) ][ ((-7 @ -1) @ (-8 >< 2))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((-1 ][ 9) >< -4) ][ 9) >< -9) >< -5) * -4) ][ -7) - -4) [] 6) + 2) >< -9) ~ -9) @ 4) - -9)\nLet C = (((((((((((((-9 @ -2) + 10) @ 3) + -10) * -8) + -8) ][ 1) - 10) + -7) + -1) + -1) * 2) + -2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a >< a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b >< b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(b + a) ][ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) ][ a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 ! b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((-7 ][ 2) ][ (-10 >< -1)) + ((4 @ -9) + (8 >< 5))) >< (((8 ! 5) * (-6 - 1)) - ((-3 * 2) * (-7 ][ -5))))\nLet B = ((((4 - 6) - (7 @ -9)) : ((-2 ! 5) ][ (-8 - -1))) ! (((6 - 7) : (7 : 10)) @ ((5 - -7) >< (5 + -9))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((-8 + -9) * 4) * 4) >< -5) + -4) : -2) ; -10) >< 10) @ -4) ; -1) ; 5) - 4) * -8) ; 3) >< 9) : 1) * -7) - 5) + 4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "73029"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a ~ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-9 >< -10) * (-6 ><++ 8)) ~ ((-6 - 7) -<> (8 <> 5))) ~<> (((7 **- 5) - (6 **~ -6)) &~& ((7 ><~ -8) *-& (-7 -<> -9))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((-3 ><~ 2) <>~* 10) - 6) - 2) >< -9) +<>& -2) * 2) ><& -4) -&& 3) ~*<> -8) &~+ 5) <>& 3) <>+ 7) - -4) &>< 9) &-- 1)\nLet C = ((((7 --* -6) -><<> (2 *+ 4)) *- ((-4 <> -7) -><~ (-7 ><- -8))) <>~ (((6 ><* -9) & (5 >< 8)) <>>< ((-4 ++ 8) *& (-9 <>-& 5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "1757"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a + a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(b ! a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a ! b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-9 @ -2) ++* (-2 @ 8)) - ((-6 ; 4) * (2 !;- 4))) -+ (((-4 +&- -2) - (-3 ++@ 5)) +@! ((7 -@ -1) &! (8 - 8))))\nLet B = ((((8 @& 7) ;@@ (6 & -3)) - ((-10 * -1) ;& (-8 & -10))) +; (((4 !- 7) +;+ (-10 &&& 9)) &+@ ((-1 &@ -8) -+ (-8 * -1))))\nLet C = ((((8 !-+ -9) +- (7 +@+ 6)) * ((-10 +;& 6) + (1 ; -7))) @ (((1 & -7) & (-1 + 8)) & ((-1 ; -7) - (9 !!- -6)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "3585"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a ][ b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ][ -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a + a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) * a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((-7 ><@* 9) >< -7) @; -2) * 10) ][ 8) @- 3) ; 4) ><><; -4) *;][ -4) * -10) >< 3) ;; -2) +** 1) ][>< -8) @ 6) *+* 3) ++ -3) *- 8) +][ 8)\nLet B = ((((7 + -8) ][ (-8 * -6)) * ((-2 - -10) ><-+ (10 +][ -1))) -][>< (((-8 ><][ 7) * (-7 @;* 6)) * ((10 + 1) @][- (-1 ][><; 7))))\nLet C = ((((-5 ;* -10) -@* (2 @;@ -2)) * ((4 ><><- 8) ][*- (-4 + -3))) ; (((7 ; 6) ><+ (2 ][ 5)) ><-][ ((5 +-- -5) -@ (-5 ; -6)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-25200"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $(b + a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 + b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a : b$ equals $(a @ b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a @ -b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-10 :: 10) @!: (5 ! 3)) -! ((1 : -4) :- (-8 @* -3))) ><>< (((-9 ><@ -6) ><*@ (4 ! -9)) +><: ((8 * 5) :@>< (-1 :@ 10))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((((-6 + -8) :@ -9) --* -5) ><! -10) - -10) +@>< 4) -!>< 6) -@ -1) -><! -1) +><+ 9) @ -9) @* 7) + -2) - -7)\nLet C = ((((-9 - -8) ! (-9 ** 7)) :>< ((10 -@ -3) :@ (-9 : -9))) :- (((-3 ><+ 6) *: (-2 ><+ -8)) *+ ((2 @ 2) >< (-5 !><* -9)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-27962"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a >< b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a >< a) * b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b >< b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a ! b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((-3 <> -1) ><! -7) *+ 2) --<> -7) <><> -8) -++ -7) *+ -3) +><- -6) **+ 6) + -7) - -7) !*- -9) -->< -6) *-- -10) +*+ 10) *<>* -3) <> -1) ><* -6)\nLet B = (((((((((((-3 -+ -4) !<> 10) *& 6) && -5) !<>- -10) !- 7) *-& 1) !& -2) *><<> -5) !>< 5) *&- -5)\nLet C = ((((((((((((((-2 !& -5) + 8) >< 6) <>-& -5) >< -2) <> -2) - 1) &* 4) +>< 4) >< -8) !& -9) &>< -8) ! 2) + 5).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 * b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((8 -][- -7) ][- 8) -+ 2) ][+~ 8) * 8) ][][* 2) -++ -8) + 10) ~ -3) *-][ -10) - 6) ][][! 2) +* 4) ][ 9) ~~ -10) !*+ -8) ~! 6) + 4) !][ 3)\nLet B = ((((5 +~ 9) -*~ (-7 & 4)) ~- ((-2 !++ 10) ! (-8 * -4))) -][- (((-2 !-! -5) ~*& (-1 &&+ 7)) ~! ((-6 && 4) + (4 - 2))))\nLet C = ((((4 +][ -3) -!+ (-2 ][][ -10)) ][][+ ((-8 ][][ -2) +*& (-6 -][~ -5))) ! (((10 --][ -10) - (-7 +! -3)) + ((-9 ~+- -8) & (9 + -2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a + a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a ~ b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a & b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 ~ b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((-7 : 9) & -5) <> -10) ~ -8) <> -7) & 10) & 9) : 6) - -9) : -6) <> -1) * -6) ~ 5) : 7) - -4) : -9) - 8) ~ 1)\nLet B = ((((-8 ~ 10) & (-5 * -10)) ][ ((-2 ~ 10) ][ (-3 ~ -5))) : (((6 <> 4) ! (5 * 1)) & ((9 ! -7) * (-2 <> -5))))\nLet C = (((((((((((-1 : -4) + -4) & -5) * -9) & 7) : 8) ~ 5) + 9) + -6) & -3) : 6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a + a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a @ b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a & b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a @ b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 - b) ; a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((-2 [] 2) @ (-7 * -8)) & ((-2 + -1) ! (4 & -3))) & (((-9 & 9) ! (-2 & -9)) ][ ((8 ; -2) ; (7 ! 10))))\nLet B = ((((3 ! 10) - (1 + 7)) ! ((7 - -3) & (-3 @ -9))) * (((-4 + 7) ! (10 ; -5)) & ((-2 ; 6) ; (-6 & 4))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((-7 ][ 4) ! -2) & 10) ][ -3) - 1) - -3) [] -10) ; 9) * 5) - 8) [] 1) ; 9) ! 2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "20950"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ; b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a ; b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ; -b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a ][ a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ][ b) + a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((10 ; -4) : (3 ][ 4)) - ((3 : -1) * (-6 ; -6))) @ (((8 >< 7) ! (2 ][ -4)) ! ((-5 * 10) >< (-5 ][ 2))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((1 >< -3) ][ -6) + 1) @ -8) @ 5) ][ 4) @ -8) - 9) >< 4) ][ -3) + -8) : 8) ][ 3) * -9) >< -4)\nLet C = ((((5 * 4) >< (-4 - -10)) ! ((-9 @ 2) ! (-9 - -5))) : (((10 - -2) : (2 >< 9)) + ((-8 ][ -5) ! (-2 ; 5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "14549"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 [] b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a [] a) : b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b [] b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a ][ b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n\nLet A = ((((3 ~ -2) ! (-10 + 6)) : ((-5 ! -1) * (-9 ! -1))) ! (((2 ~ -5) + (-4 ; 2)) - ((10 * -4) - (2 + -3))))\nLet B = ((((8 : 2) ! (-2 ~ -3)) [] ((3 * -1) : (-3 ! -5))) ~ (((5 * 8) ! (4 * -6)) ~ ((3 * 3) ~ (2 ][ 10))))\nLet C = ((((1 + -6) ][ (-1 [] 10)) ][ ((-6 ~ -10) + (-9 ][ 6))) - (((-8 + -7) - (9 : 10)) ; ((4 + 8) ][ (-6 : -3)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "157"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 * b) ~ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - a) ~ b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) ~ a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a : b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(a <> b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a >< b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-8 ! 9) ! (6 <> -9)) ! ((-10 + -8) ~ (5 & 5))) * (((8 <> -8) >< (2 * 2)) <> ((9 <> -10) - (8 >< -5))))\nLet B = ((((6 * 3) ! (5 & -5)) ! ((-5 - -6) - (-2 : -10))) + (((-6 >< 2) ! (4 ! 1)) ! ((2 <> 7) & (-7 - 5))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((-9 + 1) ~ 10) >< -9) ! 2) + 8) ~ -8) * -8) ~ -1) * -1) ! 5) & -3) ~ 9) >< 7) & 8) + 1) ! -6) ! -9) ~ 3) * -5).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-212"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 + b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a + a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a ; b$ equals $(b * a) ~ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) ~ a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((-4 @ -3) + (7 - 3)) ; ((-10 * -7) * (-9 & -5))) * (((2 & 3) & (-5 * -9)) & ((-9 - 8) - (-5 ~ 10))))\nLet B = ((((7 * 9) ~ (-10 ~ 10)) & ((6 * 6) >< (-9 @ 9))) ~ (((-4 ; -4) * (3 ~ -10)) ][ ((-7 * 4) ~ (-5 + -6))))\nLet C = ((((10 >< 7) ; (10 ; -6)) - ((-9 ; 6) ~ (2 ][ -8))) * (((-9 ][ -10) >< (3 * 5)) ; ((-8 >< 1) ][ (3 ][ -6)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "8749"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a [] b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a [] -b$.\n$a : b$ equals $(a [] b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a <> b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((((4 * -4) * -8) - 9) & 9) * -8) [] 7) * -2) : 1) - 4) : 2) : 7) ! -10) <> 3) + -2) : -9) + -9) ! -3) <> -4) [] -7) : -7) <> -7) - 8) & 9)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((-1 * -5) ! -3) & -4) ! 6) * -9) ! -4) * -6) : -4) & 1) * 6) [] 6) <> -3) - 8) + -5)\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((((((2 : 1) & 6) + -5) <> -6) & -8) [] 3) & -1) [] -10) ! -10) * -2) <> 8) [] 6) [] 1) + -7) <> -3) <> -8) & 6) : 9) - 5) - -5) [] 4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a - -b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a & b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a : b$ equals $(a & a) - b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b & b) - a$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(2 >< b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n\nLet A = ((((-2 - -1) - (-6 ! -3)) ~ ((9 - 8) @ (-6 * -1))) : (((-3 : 7) * (5 ~ 8)) : ((6 * -3) & (-3 - 5))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((((-2 - 6) * -2) * 10) ~ -5) ! 3) ~ -9) @ -3) : 2) & 5) >< 6) @ 6) @ -8) ! 2) : 8) ! 5) : 4) @ -9) ~ 7) @ -8) : 5) ~ 6)\nLet C = ((((4 : 10) - (6 & -3)) : ((-9 ~ 10) >< (8 * 5))) ! (((-7 - 3) @ (-3 & -8)) @ ((7 : -7) ! (-1 & 5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-52"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $a * b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a * a) ! b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) ! a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(b - a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) * a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((4 -- -9) - -5) <> 4) ! -4) -<> -10) +[] -8) *! 3) ++ -9) []+# -5) +[] -9) ![] 6) *<><> 3) **! -1) *!+ 5) - 5) !* 4) + 4) * 6)\nLet B = ((((((((((((5 ![] -5) + 1) -## -3) []+ 1) #<><> -9) + 8) [] -4) - 8) +[]* -8) [] 10) <>* 1) <>#* -1)\nLet C = ((((((((((((4 +* -1) - 9) []++ -7) *<>+ 1) - -9) []+ -5) !-[] 7) []+! -10) **# -5) * -5) --<> -9) - -4).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-9787"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ][ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(b * a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a & b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a & -b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((((((8 - -10) *&- -7) <>+ -8) &+ -3) <>][& 3) ][<> 6) &][][ 2) &[] 1) *[][] 8) +*[] 7) <>-* 6) ][ 8) +-[] 3) +- 5) []&<> 10) &+ -2) []&- -5) *++ -5) + 8) + 10) ][ 5) & -10)\nLet B = ((((6 +* 3) -*- (-6 <>][+ 9)) [][] ((-5 <><> -2) & (9 +* -9))) <>-[] (((6 []- -4) []<> (-6 []& -3)) - ((10 -&[] 9) -+ (-9 +&[] -2))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((-7 []<> 1) []&+ 9) <> -9) <><>+ 5) <>&+ -3) <> 7) ][+][ -7) ** 1) + -10) + 3) * 6) *<> 3) *- -8) <>][[] 8) [] -10).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 + b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a + a) : b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b + b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((((5 -:& 3) --# -2) * 9) &&: 3) #+& -10) - 2) &+* 6) *- 6) * 7) :* -9) +&- 6) - 2) # -2) # 4) +& 6) *# -7) <><> 3) : -3) :*# -2) +<> 5) <>-: 1) * -10) *#- 10)\nLet B = ((((-9 -*& -10) # (4 -#* 7)) ##<> ((5 +<>- -6) &+: (-2 + 10))) & (((2 <>:+ -7) #+ (-9 - -7)) <> ((10 +<> 4) :: (-6 <> 5))))\nLet C = (((((((((((3 :& 4) <>&# 6) <>#& -10) --- 9) -+ -10) +&& 10) *+: -8) <> 9) +# -7) * 7) + 1).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "264"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a [] b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a : b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(2 + b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a ~ a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ~ b) + a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((4 ~ -2) ><+ (5 * 10)) ~->< ((-6 ~: 8) ** (2 * 5))) - (((-10 [][]~ 2) *>< (7 -* 2)) - ((-8 ++* -4) >< (-5 ->< -5))))\nLet B = ((((2 >< 1) - (-1 ~>< 7)) *[] ((-6 -- -2) ~ (-9 *-[] 5))) ++* (((-9 *~ 9) ~- (2 -><>< 6)) >< ((-9 :*>< -4) []: (3 +~~ 10))))\nLet C = ((((-3 *[]>< -1) []><[] (-9 ><: 3)) ><~~ ((-4 ~ -8) : (10 :+ -9))) : (((-8 -~ -4) []~ (6 :~ -10)) [][]>< ((5 *[][] 3) - (6 ><- -1)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "853"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a # b$ equals $(a - a) @ b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b - b) @ a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(2 * b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((((5 - -4) []+ 10) & -8) &&- 9) @ 5) []@ 9) -+ 7) - -6) & 5) & 5) + 5) -- 10) *&+ 5) *+ 1) - -4) [][]* -8) []#& -9) *-# -1) +& -1) # -9) - -4) -- -6) [] 8)\nLet B = ((((3 +& 9) # (-9 @@[] -1)) []-@ ((9 []-- -3) * (8 #- 6))) -# (((7 [] 6) -# (10 & 2)) + ((-7 [] -10) @ (6 * 10))))\nLet C = ((((-9 @# -10) + (7 ##+ -10)) # ((6 *@- 7) +[]+ (-1 @@# 3))) + (((3 -+@ -7) &[] (-7 + -2)) #*- ((-2 + -8) ## (9 + -2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a * a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b * b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $(2 - b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a + -b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((7 #* 5) :+- (5 #: -9)) * ((7 -- 7) ><+ (8 # -1))) *-# (((3 :*& -3) #&>< (7 ++ -10)) -&>< ((-7 &+ -6) >< (10 +->< -1))))\nLet B = ((((-2 :& 9) >< (5 ><&& 1)) +# ((9 *& -4) *+ (10 ><+ 3))) *- (((5 * -4) *#- (1 :+ -5)) & ((-6 ><&& -5) * (7 : 7))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((-3 - 10) ** 9) :: 5) ><#: 9) ><-# -4) : -3) ><-: -4) ><+# 9) - 1) # 8) ><+& -9) : -5) : 1) - 7) #><& -9) -: -4) * 2) -:>< 1) #&- 7) : 5).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "15903"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a & b$ equals $(a >< b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a : b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a & a) : b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b & b) : a$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a : b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(b & a) ! b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a & b) ! a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((7 [] -4) * (-5 * -10)) >< ((-1 * -1) + (-9 [] -10))) + (((6 : 5) ! (-2 >< 10)) ! ((6 + -4) * (2 * 3))))\nLet B = ((((((((((((-10 * 10) [] 9) >< -8) + -8) ! 8) : 10) & 4) & 6) : -3) <> 8) - 7) >< -1)\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((4 >< -9) * -4) >< -10) + -2) + -6) * 7) <> 7) ! 4) >< -9) - 9) >< 3) - 2) <> -10) - 9) * 2) + 3) [] -10) [] -6).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "187"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a @ b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $a @ b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 + b) - a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((-1 *~ -10) &: 9) --@ -1) ~ -4) - 8) :~* -2) & -3) * -3) && 3) +@~ 3) +~ 6) *+ 4) - 7) +@+ 3) -& -8) -:: 9) ~ 2) : -4)\nLet B = ((((5 +:: 9) :-~ (-5 :@ -4)) &-& ((-10 :~~ -1) @& (9 @@+ -2))) & (((-6 : -1) & (7 + -8)) ~&- ((7 -+@ 5) *& (-2 ::- 7))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((9 *-+ 2) *:& 5) -:~ 9) &&* -6) ++ -6) &~ 3) @@+ 1) * 3) ~& -4) &+- 10) -- -10) &@* 7) :~ -5).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ~ b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ! b$ equals $(2 - b) ~ a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(b + a) ~ b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) ~ a$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a ~ b)$ if $a <> b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a ~ -b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((-10 <><>+ -9) !+ 9) ~ -2) >< -1) +><+ 6) ~ 7) -* -8) ++~ 6) <>-<> 7) + 9) +!>< -4) ! -9)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((((((-2 ~-- -8) >< 1) - -2) - -2) -<>+ 7) ~>< -2) * 7) - -4) +<>* 7) *<> -4) *~ 9) <>><>< 3) ! 3) -~~ -2) +* -7) ><<>* 7) ><!>< -2) !->< 8) ><!+ -1) +~- 7) -!>< 3) !- -8) ~ -10)\nLet C = ((((((((((((((-9 <>><+ 5) * 3) >< 4) ! -4) ~*~ -4) ><- 6) <>>< 4) +~! -7) +<> 1) <>+* -1) <>~>< 7) <> -10) +*~ 10) ~ -7).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ! b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a & b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a # b$ equals $a @ b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((-6 @ 6) -& 4) --& -6) @## 1) *!# 1) #& -3) -! -10) & -2) * 3) *@ 4) & -3) *# 10)\nLet B = ((((((((((((((((((((-5 - 9) * 3) -+ -9) #* -2) &!# 1) # -7) -# -4) + 2) +- -3) #*# -7) #& 5) # -6) -&+ 4) @ -7) +!- -1) #*+ -3) -- 2) * 2) @ 2) @- -2)\nLet C = ((((((((((((-8 #*@ -9) !# 8) @ -4) ** -9) !+ 8) *@ -1) +!& 3) !-# 5) +!! 10) - -6) @+@ 1) & 5).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(2 <> b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a [] b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a [] -b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-2 <> 6) [][]* (-9 *+ -10)) -<>[] ((-10 []<>][ -9) ][<>+ (7 * 7))) []-][ (((7 ][>< 3) ][<>][ (9 ><><[] -5)) -<> ((8 - -5) ][ (-6 [] 2))))\nLet B = ((((4 *<>+ 10) *<>+ (8 +<> 4)) +<> ((-2 * 6) * (-1 -<>- 3))) []][- (((5 -- 3) <>][ (-3 * -5)) <>+ ((3 +->< 9) ** (10 ** 4))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((10 [][]<> -1) ><[] 6) *][ 2) ][<> -7) - 7) *<>- -6) + 1) <>->< 7) <>+ -2) <>* -5) ><+ -5) ** 8) --<> 8) ][+[] -9) ][][>< 6) <> 1) ** 5).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-80"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a <> b$ equals $(b - a) + b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a - b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $a <> b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a ][ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = (((((((((((((((((((((2 ~ 10) ** 2) : -2) +* -4) -*~ -10) ~+ 1) +][ -10) ~+ 6) ][- 1) ][*+ -3) +:][ 10) <>:<> -1) ][ -10) - -7) + 10) ][+ 4) ][:: -8) ~-: 5) ~ 8) -<>: -6) ][-~ -3)\nLet B = ((((-10 ][- 3) - (1 ~ 6)) +<> ((2 * 6) ++* (5 ][- 2))) : (((3 ][* -3) *: (10 *: -1)) -<> ((3 -<>][ 6) :+~ (-3 : 9))))\nLet C = ((((((((((((8 <>-: -4) -:+ -6) <>:: -4) -- 6) ~][ -2) ~*+ 4) *:- -7) <>+: 6) - 6) ~-- -10) ][<>+ 1) ~++ -10).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a ! b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a * b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a - b$.\n$a @ b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(a ! a) + b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b ! b) + a$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a : b$ equals $(b * a) - b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a * b) - a$ otherwise.\n\nLet A = ((((5 @ 2) ; (5 ~ -5)) : ((10 <> -5) + (-1 ! -2))) : (((-7 * -4) ! (5 ~ -9)) - ((6 * 1) ~ (-6 ~ -8))))\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((1 ; 6) * -7) ~ -5) <> -8) @ 2) ! -8) - -8) ; -3) @ -6) ~ -10) : -1) <> -8) - -5) * -4) - -4) : -9) + -5) ! 4) : -9)\nLet C = ((((((((((((((((((((((-2 @ 3) : -5) * -3) + 3) + -9) + 2) ; -3) ; 1) ~ -4) ~ 6) ~ -10) ; 7) ! -3) <> 1) - -2) ; 4) <> -1) <> 3) - 5) @ -6) : -6) : -10).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "16344"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a : b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a [] b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a ; b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a [] b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((-1 *+: -8) *:; -3) ++[] 2) *:* 7) : 10) ; 10) + -2) :~ -10) ~*[] -9) []- -7) +[] -3) ;:* 2) ~~ -6) - 10) []; -7) []:+ -4) + 10) *~+ 5)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((((((((-9 [] -9) [] -6) :+ 10) +~ -5) :~~ 9) * -1) :~ 3) +++ -9) : -3) :;: -7) []* -1) :+ -9) *~- 3) -;[] -1) [] 1) ~*: 8) +; -9) * -10) [];[] -4) ~;* -3) ~: -3) :~ 6) ~;; 4)\nLet C = ((((((((((((5 ~ 8) * 5) :~; 10) : -10) ; 1) -:: 2) * 8) -- -6) *~ 4) :~ -2) +[] 2) ~ -2).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-63873"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $a + b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(2 + b) <> a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a @ b$ equals $(a + b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-1 >< 6) + (-10 <>+>< 1)) &><>< ((-7 & 10) +@ (-7 *@ -6))) <><> (((-4 @& 10) @ (6 - 4)) - ((10 <>@<> -10) * (2 ><<>- 5))))\nLet B = ((((-6 -@* 10) *& (5 + 9)) *-@ ((4 * 4) ><-- (2 @ 5))) +@ (((10 *-& -4) @ (-5 --& 3)) *<> ((6 -<>* -1) - (-10 &@ -2))))\nLet C = (((((((((((((((((2 @><- -1) +-& -3) *><* 6) +@- 3) -- 8) - -8) + -1) ><<> 4) >< -4) ><++ -6) - -10) &@>< -2) *<><> -10) @ 4) <> 8) -><+ -8) @@ -1).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "230"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a # b$ equals $(2 - b) * a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a [] b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\n$a & b$ equals $(a # b)$ if $a - b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a # -b$.\n$a ][ b$ equals $a - b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((((((-8 +- 10) -#- 6) -* 9) ][ 1) ][-- 1) -][ 5) + 8) ][ 3) -+ -3) -- 6) -][ -7) ][*& -5) [] -7) []+ -1) --& -5) # -6) &*- 3) ][+ 5) + -10) -## -9)\nLet B = (((((((((((((((((-10 + -3) + -2) - 4) # -4) *][ 6) + -8) ][# -7) ++- -2) []&* -7) &## 8) ][ 4) ][ -4) ][ 10) *++ 4) &* 3) [] 7) +*[] 10)\nLet C = ((((8 #&- -2) &-][ (7 &-+ 8)) -+ ((-9 []# -3) []+ (3 &-- 10))) []][# (((-9 #- -10) #& (3 + -10)) -* ((4 -*+ -7) # (10 & 2)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "10086"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a <> b$ equals $(b + a) * b$ if $|a-b| < 2$ and $(a + b) * a$ otherwise.\n$a # b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $a <> b$ if $gcd(a, b) == 1$ and $gcd(a, b)$ otherwise, where gcd stands for greatest common divisor.\n$a & b$ equals $(a - b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a + b$.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((-9 &! -9) &#+ (10 #&# -3)) &!+ ((2 & 5) ## (3 -- -10))) * (((4 * -5) *- (-10 #- 9)) & ((5 -- 6) & (2 &+& 10))))\nLet B = ((((7 <><> 7) -# (7 ++ 8)) && ((-3 # 5) - (-6 &<># 9))) !# (((9 +&- 3) +-+ (-3 ## 9)) - ((-5 <>&* -9) * (8 - -2))))\nLet C = ((((-7 &#! 6) && (8 <><> -8)) -<> ((6 <> -1) -*+ (3 <> 2))) #* (((-5 - -9) & (-2 ! -9)) & ((-10 #+ -1) #!+ (-2 * 5)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "6449"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following new operations:\n\n$a & b$ equals $min(a, b)$ if either $a$ or $b$ is prime and $max(a, b)$ otherwise.\n$a <> b$ equals $(2 & b) + a$ if $a > b$ and $b$ otherwise.\n$a ! b$ equals $(a & b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $a * b$.\n$a >< b$ equals $(a * b)$ if $a + b > 0$; otherwise,  it equals $-a * -b$.\n$a ~ b$ equals $(a & a) >< b$ if $b < 2$ and $(b & b) >< a$ otherwise.\nFor brevity, we use $a <op1><op2> b$ to denote $(a op1 b) op2 b$. For example, $4 +* -5$ means $(4 + -5) * -5$ and $4 *-- -5$ means $(4 * -5) -- -5$.\nLet A = ((((((((((((((((1 *! 9) ! 3) ~ 1) &- 5) !+ 7) ~! -9) !~- 6) >< -10) + 7) -<> -6) ><~ 3) +~<> 9) ><-* 10) ->< -10) <><> -5) ->< 2)\nLet B = (((((((((((3 - 5) &++ -2) & -3) *+ 4) !+& 3) ++- 7) <> -6) +- 8) + 4) ><- -5) ~! 7)\nLet C = ((((-10 *+ 10) ><- (-8 &*~ -9)) &+ ((-4 ><~~ 9) &! (3 <><> 9))) ! (((7 && 5) *>< (-7 + 7)) +~ ((-8 & 10) & (3 -*>< 6)))).\nCompute A + B - C. Your final answer must be in number form.",
    "answer": "-58984"
  }
]
